awe.sm 2016-02-16

# Privacy Policy | Unified Social | Unified

Unified Social, Inc. is an enterprise social media advertising technology company. This privacy policy ("Policy") describes how we obtain and treat information on behalf of our advertisers, agencies, data partners and other businesses ("Clients") that use our advertising technology (“Platform”), and on behalf of ourselves on our corporate website located at www.unifiedsocial.com ("Website"). This Policy also describes how we treat personally identifiable information that we obtain via our products and services (“Services”), including our Website, and that may be provided to us by our third party partners. 

For the purposes of this Policy, we will use interchangeably the terms "Unified", "we", "us", "our" and the like to refer to Unified Social, Inc. and its subsidiaries and affiliates, collectively. We will notify you if we materially change this Policy, at which time you will have the opportunity to discontinue using our Services. You agree to this Policy when you access or use the Website and/or use our Services, some of which may be made available through the Website. 

#### Safe Harbor Privacy Principles

We comply with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. We have certified that Unified Social adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification page, please visit [http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/](https://www.export.gov/safeharbor/). 

## PRIVACY PRACTICES FOR OUR WEBSITE

* * *

#### Personally Identifiable Information ("PII")

We may collect PII from the Website when you elect to provide PII to us. PII is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to information such someone's name, address, telephone number, mobile number and/or email address. For example, you may choose to send us PII about yourself in an email or by completing an online form or filling out a questionnaire or survey on our Website, or on the website of one of our clients or partners. Once collected, we will store your PII for as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill your requests and for record keeping purposes. 

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information ("non-PII") from visitors to this Website. In general, this is information that by itself cannot be used to identify a particular person or entity, and may include your IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, Internet browsing and usage habits, your internet service provider, domain name, the time/date of your visit to this Website, the referring URL and your computer's operating system. We use this information to understand our Website traffic, the general demographics and other patterns of visitors to our website and more generally to improve our products and services. We’ve enabled Google Analytics on this Website to help us collect and process information on the Website. We may provide aggregated non-PII about our users to third parties for audit, marketing research and other purposes. 

If you'd like us to delete any PII that you have provided to us, please send your request to us at [support@unifiedsocial.com](mailto:support@unifiedsocial.com) and we will process your request within a reasonable period of time after receipt. 

#### Cookies

Like most websites, we use "cookies" and web beacons to help us manage our Website. Cookies are small text files that contain a string of alphanumeric characters. Web beacons (also known as "1X1 pixels" or "clear GIFs") are small strings of code that provide a method for delivering a graphic image on a web page or in an email message for the purpose of transferring data. You have the option of blocking the use of cookies by changing a setting in your browser. You can check your browser supplier's website for details on how to do this. For more information about cookies and web beacons please visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/cookies). 

#### Third Party Websites

The Website may contain links to and advertisements for websites operated by third parties whose privacy practices may differ from ours. While we endeavor to associate only with reputable entities, we cannot be responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties. It is your responsibility to check the privacy policies of all websites that you visit. 

## PRIVACY PRACTICES FOR OUR PLATFORM

* * *

#### Our Platform

Our Platform is designed to enable our Clients to purchase advertising on social media platforms such as Facebook, Twitter and LinkedIn and to report on the progress of such campaigns. Pursuant to offering the Services, we obtain information, which may include PII, from our Clients and third party data partners, which we use to provide our media planning and buying services and for the execution and delivery of the media purchases made using our Platform. We may collect non-PII regarding a user's behavior and usage patterns on advertisements and sites operated by our Clients to better customize the type of advertisements users see on various sites. We may also collect non-PII via the Platform, including but not limited to an Internet user's IP host address, pages viewed, browser type, the URL, the referring URL, Internet Service Provider, and his or her computer's operating system. In order to execute some of the Services via our Platform, we may also need to share some of this information with our third party partners that provide certain services to us. When requested, we may also employ this information in a compiled format without identifying users specifically to provide to our Clients precise profiles of the types of individuals responding to their advertising and promotional activities. 

#### The Awe.sm Sharing Tool

Our Services include the Awe.sm sharing tool, which enables our Clients to create sharing links. These links help Users share posts and other social media content created by our Clients, and help our Clients gain insight into how their social media posts are shared. In order to facilitate the Awe.sm sharing tool, we collect information via Awe.sm, including: the social media user name of the sharer (when publicly available), the IP address, device type and operating system of the computer or device that is facilitating the share, the referring URL and the URL being shared. Some of this information may be considered PII. Some of this information may also be used by our Clients to inform their advertising programs via our Platform. 

#### Cookies

Our Clients may use cookies in conjunction with Web beacons. Pursuant to providing the Services, we also use cookies and web beacons. Web beacons allow us to record that a user has visited a particular webpage along with additional non-PII that the website publisher or advertiser may choose to include with that pixel. Most Internet browsers enable users to block or delete cookies. Please note that cookies are used for a variety of reasons, so disabling or deleting them may adversely impact your overall online experience. 

#### Information Security, Data Integrity

We take precautions - including technical, administrative and physical measures - to safeguard your information. We use technical safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption. Your account information including email address is located on a secured server behind a firewall. We authorize access to PII, including email addresses, only for those employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. We also enforce physical access controls to our buildings and files. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect PII, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. We process information in a way that is compatible with and relevant for the purpose for which it was collected. To the extent necessary for those purposes, we take reasonable steps to ensure that any information in our care is accurate, complete, current and reliable for its intended use. 

#### Ad Choices / Opt-out

Unified uses third-party advertising partners who collect non-PII via this Website to tailor advertising messages on other Websites. We are supportive of the Network Advertising Initiative and Digital Advertising Alliance self-regulatory programs for behavioral advertising. If you would like more information about behavioral advertising and would like to understand more about your privacy choices, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](https://www.aboutads.info/choices/) or [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](https://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/). Currently, the standards regarding the Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals and appropriate responses are not defined. Accordingly, we do not assign a meaning to DNT signals. 

#### Access to Information

Unified will allow an individual access to their PII to the extent it is available and allow the individual to correct, amend or delete inaccurate information, except where the burden or expense of providing access would be disproportionate to the risks to the privacy of the individual in the case in question or where the rights of persons other than the individual would be violated. 

#### Privacy Rights of Children

Our Website and Services are designed for those 18 years of age and older. We do not knowingly collect PII from anyone under the age of 13. If we are made aware that we have received PII from someone under 13, we will use reasonable efforts to remove that information from our records. 

#### Disclosure of Information to Third Parties, Onward Transfer

The PII we obtain via the Platform is subject to the privacy policies of our Clients, and Unified only processes such information as directed by Clients. We do not sell, rent or share PII collected on the Website with non-affiliated third parties without your consent. We may share PII with trusted third party contractors who provide services for us. These third party contractors are prohibited from using the information we provide for purposes other than performing services for us. We may also disclose information collected through our Services and information derived from our Services to our Clients. 

We may disclose information on our servers to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including but not limited to, fraud and situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. Finally, we may transfer information, including any PII, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets, bankruptcy, or other corporate change. 

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, please send us an email at [support@unifiedsocial.com](mailto:support@unifiedsocial.com). 

#### Privacy Complaints by European Union and Swiss Citizens

In compliance with the U.S.-EU and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Unified Social commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union and Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact us at [support@unifiedsocial.com](mailto:support@unifiedsocial.com). 

We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU Safe Harbor, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by the privacy department at Unified Social, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](https://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint. 

Council of Better Business Bureaus, Inc.  
BBB EU Safe Harbor  
3033 Wilson Boulevard, Suite 600  
Arlington, VA 22201  
U.S.A.  

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

* * *

We may update this Policy at any time. The latest version of this Policy will always be available via prominent link from our Website. Please check this page occasionally to make sure you are aware of any updates. 

_Last revised December 2014. Copyright © 2014 Unified Social, Inc. All Rights Reserved_
